One dive. One breath. One chance.
The Deepest Breath is a documentary film directed by Laura McGann.
Bonded by their love of freediving, a record-setting champion and a heroic safety
diver try to make history with a remarkable feat, ready to risk it all.
Self - Freediver, played by Alessia Zecchini.
Self - Deceased Freediver /Self - Safety Diver, played by Stephen Keenan.
Self - Respiratory Therapist, played by Leigh Baker.
Self - Scuba Diver, played by Mahmoud Barracuda.
Self - Freediver Italian National Team, played by Ilaria Boni.
Self - Freediver, played by Kristof Coenen.
The Deepest Breath is a 2023 documentary film directed and written by Laura McGann that profiles Italian freediver Alessia Zecchini on her quest
to break a world record with the help of safety diver Stephen Keenan and her competition against Japanese freediver Hanako Hirose.
The film explores themes of diving, deep sea,
apnoe-diving, extreme sports, based on true story.
The tone is thought_provoking.